Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Flyers, 1977-1985
  - Sounds of the City at The Royal Villa Play House, 1980-04-26; Phoenix Drill Team Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Bambaataa, Jazzy-Jay, Red-Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s, The Mighty Zulu Nation
    157
    New Haven, Connecticut
  - A Love Squigg & Nubian Prod. At T-Connection, 1980-05-04; Love Squigg Productions; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.'s
    45
  - A Solar Ultra Funk Jam Disco at Bronx River Ctr., 1980-05-09; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy-Jay, Red Alert, Soulsonic Force M.C.s, Grandmaster Flash, Funk Machine, Imperial 4 M.C.s
    153
  - "A Love Squigg" & "Earth Quake" Production at Rodbenders Club, 1980-05-09; Love Squigg Productions; Earth Quake Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Rob Gold, Mix Master & The Devastating "4" MCs, "Malibu", "Rob Ski", "Tricky Tee", "Harry O"
    199
  - Star Guard Productions Presents the Ultimate in a Super Jam Boogie at The Ace Community Center, 1980-05-12; Star Guard Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    Afrika Bambaata, Jazzy-Jay, Spoonie Gee and the Treacherous 3, Pleasure II and Mr. Nel, The Cosmic force M.C.s, Soul Sonic force M.C.s, Mr. Biggs/Pow-Wow/Lisa Lee/Ice-Ice/Globe, D.J. Red Alert, The Crash Crew, T.J. Swan
    17
  - A Sure Shot Body Rock at Pilgrim State Assembly Hall, 1980-05-17; Smith-Allen Productions; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s
    102
    Brentwood, New York
  - A Disco Tribute to the Flyer Men at Bronx River Community Center, 1980-05-30; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Buddy Esquire, Eddie Ed, Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Breakout, Baron, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s, Funky 4 plus 1, Brothers Disco, Mighty Zulu Nation
    156
  - The True Elements of Funk at Rodbenders Club, 1980-06-06; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D. J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, D.J. Superman, D.J. Afrika Islam
    42
  - Senior Weekend 1980 at T-Connection, 1980-06-06-1980-06-07; Brothers Disco, The; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    The Brothers Disco, Breakout, Baron, Funky 4 plus 1, Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soulsonic Force M.C.s
    152
  - Westchester's Senior Day Disco Dance Part 2 at Morris St. Center, 1980-06-20-1980-06-21; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soulsonic Force M.C.s
    134
  - The Summers of the 80s at Jackson Street Center, 1980-08-09; Solo Sounds (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Easy-E & The Vicious 5 MCs, D.J. Banana Joe, Shaun Ski, Lorie Lor, Kool J, JJ Swan, Sweet Me-Me, D.J. Africa Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay & The SoulSonic Force MCs
    120
  - A Zulu Nation Tribute to the D.J.'s of New York at The T. Connection Disco, 1980-09-12; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.'s, Cosmic Force M.C.'s
    36
  - A Birthday Disco Baasshhh for "Trouble" at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1980-09-20 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Mean Gene, Fantasy 4 MC's
    166
  - The Freeze Show Special at C&C Disco, 1980-10-04; Cold Rush Unlimited (Box 547, Folder B)
    Mr. Freeze, Kenny Sex Dollar Bill, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy J, Red Alert, Soulsonic Force, Rayvon Johnny Wa, White Flash Dizzy D, Pernellio
    39
  - A Disco Tribute to the Rap Recording Artists at T-Connection, 1980-10-10; Nubian Productions; Squigg Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Love Squigg, Devestating Force, Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force & Cosmic Force MC's
    197
  - Halloween Disco at The Rink, 1980-10-31 (Box 547, Folder B)
    The Crash Crew, D.J. African Bambaataa, Zulu Nation, The Disco Twins
    21
  - The Zulu Nations 5th Double Night Anniversary Disco Tribute to Sly and the Family Stone and James Brown!! At Bronx River Community Center and T-Connection, 1980-11-07-1980-11-08; Nubian Productions; Zulu Nation (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s, Cosmic Force M.C.s
    202
  - A Super Jam Throw Down Disco at Bronx River Center, 1980-11-15; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, D.J. Soul Sonic Force, Cosmic Force M.C.s, D.J. Breakout, D.J. Baron, The Funky 4 plus 1, Trecherous 3 mc's
    181
  - Solo Sound at 35 Jackson St., 1980-11-29 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Easy E, D.J. Banana Joe, Vicious 5 MC, D.J. Africa Bambaataa, Crash-Crew, C.B. Crew
    113
  - Ecstasy Garage Disco presents A Birthday Bang!, 1980-12-13 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Kool A.J., Theodore & Fantastic 5, Wayne & Charlew, M.C. Starsky, D.J. Smalls
    177
  - The Bronx Dance-A-Thon at Bronx River Center, 1980-12-13; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force, Cosmic Force, The Cold Crush Bro.'s, D.J. Charlie Chase, D.J. Tony Tone, Cold Crush 4 M.C.'s, Theodore
    184
  - The M.C. "Throwdown" Showdown/A Holiday Smoka at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1980-12-26-1980-12-29 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Coldcrushers 4, Grandmaster Caz, Almighty Kay-Gee, Jerry D-Lewis, Easy-A.D., Kool D.J. A.J., D.J. Smalls, Starsky, Theodore, Fantastic 5.
    160
  - Rockin with the Stars at the T-Connection, 1981-01-10; Nubian Productions; Squigg Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Love Squigg, Devastating 4 M.C.s, Grandmaster Jaz, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s, Cosmic Force M.C.s, Cold Crush 4 emcee's.
    193
  - A Yonkers N.Y. Funk, Jam, Disco at Jackson St. Center, 1981-01-17; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s, Cosmic Force M.C.s, D.J. Banana Joe.
    100
  - An Arabian Nights Fantasy at Black Berry Jam, 1981-02-07; The Super-Stars (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and Final Edition.
    12
    Bayshore, Long Island
  - The Funk is on Disco at Bronx River Center, 1981-02-21; Gents Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Grand Master Flash, Furious 5 M.C.s, Afrika Bambaataa, Cosmic Force, Soul Sonic Force, Mean Machine.
    107
  - Battle Time 10, 1981-03-13 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Africa Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Cosmic Force, vs. Kool Herc, Wiz Kid, Clark Kent, Ultimate 3.
    203
  - Ecstasy Garage Disco Presenting AA First Anniversary "Supathrowdown", 1981-03-21 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Kool D.J. AJ & Busy Bee, The Crash Crew #1, The Coldcrush Four.
    146
  - AA Grand Wizard Master Mash Up! AA Double Birthday Celebration Jam at Ecstasy Garage DiscoJam, 1981-03-28 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Wiz Theodore, Master Rob, Fantastic 5, Charley Chase & Tony Tone with The Coldcrush 4.
    145
  - AAA Boss Birthday Sure Shot at Ecstasy Garage Disco, 1981-04-10 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Doc La-Rock, The Kid Wizard Gregski, Grand Imperial D.J. Kenny Ken, MC Love Hutch, D.J. Patty Duke, D.J. Mike, Darry-D, The Sinister Rock, Debbie-D, Jazzy Ace.
    186
  - Harlem World Presents The Funk Machine, The Crash Crew, The Cold Crush, 1981-04-24-1981-04-25 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Outlaw 4
    131
  - Wednesday 29, Night Jam at Bronx River Center, 1981-04-29; The Organization (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa & Zambu, Mr. Biggs, D.J. Afrika Islam & Ed. LA Rock.
    135
  - 1st Annual D.J. Award Presentation at The Rink, 1981-05-15; DT Corporation (Box 547, Folder C)
    Grand Master Flash, Furious 5, Kurtis Blow, Master-D, Sweet G, Crash Crew, D.J. Afrika Bambaata, D.J. Sesame, Count Cool Out, Baby-D, Eddie Cheba, D.J. Hollywood, The Disco Twins, Infinity Machine, King Charles, Disco Four, Grand Wizard Theodore, D.J. Smalls, Lady Love, Treacherous-3, Sweety-G.
    162
  - Dance Music at T-Connection, 1981-05-15; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Soul Sonic Force M.C.s.
    187
  - "Spin-A-Thon" at Roosevelt Roller Rink, 1981-05-22; DT Corporation (Box 547, Folder C)
    Mr. Magic, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and the Zulu Nation.
    128
  - The Battle of the Sound Systems at T-Connection, 1981-05-24; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Lil Rock, MC Jay Bee & Geramano vs. D.J. Afika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Cosmic Force MC's.
    129
  - A Birthday Baash for "Slim" at Your Spot, 1981-05-30 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Islam, Funk Mach, Bambaataa, Disco 4, Cold Crush Bros., Busy-Bee & A.J. Theodore, D.J. Warren Wood, The Jazzy 5 Emcees, Feva Dee, Kid Finesse.
    185
  - "The Hell Raisin' Hip Hopp" Hoedown at Ecstasy Productions 2 Hunts Point Palace Blast, 1981-06-06 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Afrika Bambaataa and Soulsonic Force Emcees.
    22
  - Rock & Soul at Your Spot, 1981-06-26; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Cosmic Force MCs.
    179
  - For the First Time in Jersey..New York's Master of Records..at Christopher Columbus Hall, 1981-06-27 (Box 547, Folder B)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, CosmicForce M.C.s, Chubby Chub, Lisa Lee, Ikey C, Ice Ice.
    23
  - A Love Squigg Birthday Festivity at T-Connection, 1981-06-28; Malibu Productions; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy-Jay, The Cosmic Force M.C.'s, D.J. Love Squigg, M.C. Malibu, Female Equality, D.J. Wanda-Dee, The Dynasty 2 M.C.'s, Lil. Dave.
    105
  - A Hip Hop Family Reunion Jam Pt. 2 at Roller World Skating Rink, 1981-07-03 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Cosmic Force MCs, Breakout Funky 4 plus 1.
    176
  - A Square Biz Jam Funk Disco Explosion at The Ritz Roller Rink, 1981-07-31 (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Soul Sonic Force MC's.
    144
  - Afrika Bambaataa at C.Y.O., 1981-10-03; D-Best (Box 547, Folder A)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and the Mighty Zulu Nation, the Cosmic Force, and the Soulsonic Force MCs.
    8
    Patterson, New Jersey
  - Back by Popular Demand The One's Who Funk Up Any Land at Cava Foundation Center, 1981-10-23; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force, Cosmic Force M.C.'s.
    140
  - A Pre-Black Solidarity Day Funk Jam at the C.Y.O., 1981-10-30; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Soul Sonic Force, Cosmic Force.
    182
  - A Thanksgiving Eve Throwdown at Edenwald Center, 1981-11-25 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Kool Herc & Family, The Whiz Kid & The Turnout Crew, D.J. Wanda-Dee & The Jazzy 3 M.C.'s.
    136
  - Reggae at the Left Bank, 1981-11-29 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Mikey Jarrett, Horace Andy, KC White, Prince Junior.
    161
    Mount Vernon, New York
  - Umoja (Unity) Funk Jam Nite Part-2 at T-Connection, 1981-12-11; Eddie Ed; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder A)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Soul Sonic Force, and Cosmic Force.
    14
  - Umoja (Unity) Funk Jam Nite Part 2 at T Connection, 1981-12-11 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Soul Sonic Force, Cosmic Force, Cotton Candy.
    19
  - Rhythm & Funk JamDisco at Bayshore YMCA, 1981-12-12; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy-Jay, D.J. Red Alert, Cosmic Force MCs.
    170
    Long Island, New York
  - The Disco Sounds of the Master Ice at Kips Bay Boys Club, 1981-12-19; Sly Crew (Box 547, Folder C)
    Master Ice, Jazzy 5 emcees, Bam, Jazzy, Red, Cool Bee, Courtney, John Shaft.
    149
  - T Connection Presents A Jamaican & Hip Hop Holiday Sure Shot, 1981-12-26 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Rankin Ric, Rankin Stone, Bigga Rank, Papa Flash, The Upsetter, The Bossforce.
    20
  - A Sunday Nite Electronic Funkadelic Jam at P.A.L., 1981-12-27; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Solo Sounds, D.J. Easy-E, Jazzy 5.
    150
  - A Three Day Holiday Jam at T Connection, 1981-12-28-1981-12-29; Richie-T Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Cold Crush Bro's, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy-Jay, Red-Alert, Jazzy 5 Emcees.
    147
  - City Wide "Boro Boogithon" at The Audubon Ballroom, 1981-12-31 (Box 547, Folder C)
    The Treacherous 3, Mr. Sweety Gee, Staten I's Dr. Rock & Force M.C.s, The Boogie Boys.
    143
  - The Super Hi-Powered Birthday Party 82! For Grandmaster Flash at Harlem World Disco, 1982-01-02 (Box 547, Folder B)
    .Bambaataa, Kool D.J. AJ & Busy B Starsky, Theodore, Treacherous 3, Rockin Rob, Sugar Hill Gang, Sequence, Mean Machine, Funky 4, Crash Crew, Spoony Gee
    18
  - A Sureshot Party Crew "For You" Presentation at Negril, 1982-02-11 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Treacherous 3.
    122
  - Black History Month Annual Cultural Freebee Jam at Bronx River Center, 1982-02-25; Afrika Bambaataa; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Cold Crush Brothers, Charlie Chase, Tony Tone, Cold Crush 4, Kool Ero, Jazzy Jay, Soul Power 82, Red Alert, Afrika Bambaataa, Soulsonic & Cosmic Force, Jazzy 5, Grandmaster Flash, Furious Lovers, Kool D.J. AJ & Busy Bee Starski, Grand Wizard Theodor, Fantastic 5, Breakout & Funky 4, Trecherous 3, Double Trouble, Solo Sounds, Whiz Kid, Afrika Islam, Billy Boy & Mark V, The Just 4 & DST & Infinity 4.
    96
  - The Throwdown for 82 at OnWheels Roller Rank, 1982-03-06 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Imperial Wizard, Terrible Tee.
    98
  - The Wheels of Steel formerly Negril Thursday Nites at Danceteria, 1982-03-23 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Bambaataa, EmCee E.C., The Rocksteady #1 B-Boys, Theodore, The Zulu Nation.
    141
  - An Electric Boogie Skate Dance ShowDown!!!! At Studio 59, 1982-03-27; Wheels "Plus" (Box 547, Folder C)
    Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Jazzy 5 MCs.
    124
    Nanuet, New York
  - Wheels of Steel Nite at Danceteria, 1982-03-30; KLB Production (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa, D.J. Jazzy Jay, Female Rap Silverstar, Lil Markey Cee, Lil Sput #1.
    137
  - Funk At It's Best!!! At Roosevelt High School, 1982-05-22; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Soulsonic Force.
    127
  - The Soul Sonic Force at Skate World, 1982-05-28; DT Corporation (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and the Disco Twins, D.J. Smalls & Sesame, Flash Master & The Rockwell Crew.
    139
    Queens, New York
  - Memorial Day Spring Throwdown at Upskate New York, 1982-05-30 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Soulsonic Force.
    114
    New Windsor, New York
  - "Planet Rock" Show & Dance at Davis Armory, 1982-06-11; Concepts Unlimited; W.O.K.B. (Box 547, Folder B)
    Soul Sonic Force.
    28
    Orlando, Florida
  - Live in Concert Soul Sonic Force at Mad Hatter, 1982-07-24 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Soul Sonic Force, Odessey & Company, Fabulations Band, Preacherman.
    151
  - The Soul Sonic Force Live in Concert with Their Hit Single "Planet Rock" at Kim Graves, 1982-07-25 (Box 547, Folder C)
    126
    Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
  - Soul Sonic Force "Planet Rock" at Washington Coliseum, 1982-08-06 (Box 547, Folder C)
    Soul Sonic Force, Rare Essence, E.U., The Mighty Peacemakers, Redds and the Boys, Tricky Rick.
    133
    Washington, D.C.
  - Planet Rock with Soul Sonic Force at Rollerdome, 1982-08-08 (Box 547, Folder C)
    178
    Hamden, Connecticut
  - Soul Sonic Force Planet Rock at Stages/Smart Bar, 1982-08-17 (Box 547, Folder B)
    Afrika Bambaataa.
    25
    Chicago, Illinois
  - Calling all Schools! To African Head Shop Big Planet Rock Back to School Blast at Sports Acres, 1982-08-23 (Box 547, Folder B)
    26
  - Back to School, End of Summer Party at Walter's Lake, 1982-08-26 (Box 547, Folder A)
    Soulsonic Force, Sequence Eight, and the Howard Brothers.
    3
    Augusta, Georgia
  - Huge Pisces Party at United Skates of America, 1982-09-03; Y.S.S. Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    L.A. Sunshine, Greg "G", T Ski Valley, Mr. Magic, D.J. Afrika Bambaataa and his Zulu Nation with the Jazzy 5, Quicksilver and the Super Lover M. Cee's.
    99
    Jackson Heights, New York
  - A New Year Eve at C.C.P. Rec., 1982-12-31; Soundtwo Productions (Box 547, Folder C)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Soul Sonic Force, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert.
    168
  - Shows at the Peppermint Lounge, 1983-02-17 (Box 547, Folder A)
    Afrika Bambaataa and The Jazzy 5.
    13
    Manhattan, New York
  - Thursday Nights Live at Celebrity Club, 1983-02-24; Herman M (Box 547, Folder C)
    169
  - The Rappers Awards of 1983 All Performing Live in Stage, 1983-02-26; Broadway International (Box 547, Folder C)
    D.J. Mr. Magic, Jazzee Five, Disco Four, Africa Bambaataa & His Soul Sonic Force.
    115
  - Celebrity D.J. Series: Afrika Bambaataa, The Godfather of Hip-Hop & The Renegade of Funk at University Club, 1984-11-16 (Box 547, Folder C)
    132
  - Black History Monthly 4th Annual Cultural Freebee Jam at Bronx River Center, 1985-02-26; Bambaataa; Nubian Productions (Box 547, Folder B)
    Afrika Bambaataa, Jazzy Jay, Red Alert, Afrika Islam, Kool Herc Lisa Lee, Sha Rock, Cold Crush Bros. Force AID's, Ikey C, Starski, Dst, Whiz Kid, LG.
    29
- Photographs, 1975-2004
  - Dark red leather album, 1977-1982 (Box 534)
    Includes candid photos and group shots.
  - Green leather album, 1977-1982 (Box 535)
    Includes snapshots of shows and portraits.
  - Red album, 1977-1982 (Box 536)
    Includes snapshots of shows/DJing, candid photos, and photos from Africa.
  - Yellow album, 1977-1982 (Box 537)
    Includes snapshots of Soulsonic Force shows and group photos.
  - Blue album, 1976-1980 (Box 538)
    Annotated album containing photos of Bambaataa and friends.
  - Green album, 1976-1980 (Box 538)
    Annotated album containing photos of Bambaataa, friends, and the UZN.
  - Patterned album, 1976-1980 (Box 538)
    Annotated album containing photos of the Savage Spades and Bambaataa's trip to Africa/Europe.
  - Brown album, 1976-1980 (Box 539)
    Includes performance photos, candid shots, and group shots.
  - Our Family album, 1975 (Box 540)
    Annotated album primarily containing concert photos (Sly and the Family Stone, James Brown) and Elijah Muhammad news clippings.
  - Flower album, 1975 (Box 540)
    Annotated album containing concert photos (Sly and the Family Stone, Graham Central Station), friends, family, Pywackett.
  - Dog album, 1975 (Box 540)
    Annotated album containing photos of the Savage/Black Spades, friends, and Bambaataa's Africa trip, as well as news clippings and a death certificate related to a police shooting in the Bronx.
  - Bambaataa photos, 1988-2004 (Box 550, Folder 1)
  - Snapshots and travel photos, 1990-2004 (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - Early photos, 1980 (Box 540, Folder 1)
- Personal Papers, 1971-2005
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Personal documents, 1971-1984 (Box 524, Folder 15)
  - Tommy Boy contract, 1982 (Box 546, Folder 9)
    Unsigned copy of contract between Afrika Bambaataa and the Soulsonic Force and Tommy Boy Music.
  - Nubian Productions incorporation documents, 1982 (Box 550, Folder 5)
  - Disco Beats, 1982-07-01; Lewis, Tom (Box 545, Folder 12)
    Vol. 6, no. 7
  - Dance Beats, 1982-09-01 (Box 545)
    Vol. 3, no. 9
  - MC Globe lyrics, 1983 (Box 546, Folder 8)
    Printed lyrics sheet for "Looking for the Perfect Beat" on Tommy Boy letterhead.
  - Appearances, performances, 1984-1999 (Box 550, Folder 4)
  - Biographies, 1984-2002 (Box 546, Folder 10)
  - Tommy Boy verification of employment letter, 1985-03-27 (Box 546, Folder 22)
  - Jam on the Groove scene outlines, 1989 (Box 548, Folder 4)
  - South Africa project, 1990 (Box 546, Folder 20)
  - Bambaataa backstage passes, 1991 (Box 546, Folder 23)
  - Zulu Nation Management, 1992-06 (Box 548, Folder 10)
    Letter from Amad Henderson to Ice T and Ice Cube.
  - Planet Rock press release, 1993 (Box 548, Folder 9)
  - Zulu Nation - Double Xposure memorandum, 1994 (Box 550, Folder 6)
  - Rock N Roll Hall of Fame, 1994-1995 (Box 550, Folder 8)
  - Songs, copyrights, 1995 (Box 550, Folder 7)
  - Spades War Counsel Award, 1996 (Box 549, Folder 3)
  - Book proposal, 1996 (Box 550, Folder 9)
  - East coast/West coast issues, 1996-04 (Box 546, Folder 18)
  - Appearances, performances, 2000-2001 (Box 550, Folder 10)
  - Appearances, performances, 2002 (Box 550, Folder 11)
  - Appearances, performances, 2003 (Box 550, Folder 12)
  - Hollywood Walk of Fame nomination package, 2004 (Box 548, Folder 11)
  - r a g e library book, 2004 (Box 491)
  - Universal Federation for the Preservation of Hip Hop Culture, 2005 (Box 548, Folder 6)
  - Appearances, performances, 2006 (Box 550, Folder 13)
  - Smithsonian - Collecting initiative launch, 2006 (Box 550, Folder 14)
  - Afrika Bambaataa and Family Rider Requirements, Undated (Box 546, Folder 11)
  - Planet Rock stationary, Undated (Box 546, Folder 13)
  - Press About Bambaataa, 1980-1996
    - Bambaataa press, 1980-1989 (Box 532, Folder 1)
    - Clippings scrapbook, 1981-1983 (Volume 3)
    - Bambaataa/James Brown press, 1984-1992 (Box 532, Folder 8)
    - Bambaataa bio, 1986 (Box 532, Folder 2)
    - Hip Hop Connection magazine, 1989 (Box 532, Folder 3)
    - Bambaataa flyers, leaflets, promo, 1990-2000 (Box 532, Folder 10)
    - UZN/Bambaataa press, 1990-1999 (Box 532, Folder 4)
    - Shango, 1991 (Box 532, Folder 5)
    - Bambaataa bio - original paste-up, 1992 (Box 532, Folder 6)
    - DJ Red Alert on Zulu nation, 1993 (Box 532, Folder 7)
    - Press, 1995-1996 (Box 532, Folder 12)
    - Jack the Rapper, 1986-10-22 (Box 545, Folder 10)
    - The Contact Sheet, 1990-10-01 (Box 545, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous press, Undated (Box 532, Folder 11)
    - Sure's Salutes: Afrika Bambaataa, Undated (Box 532, Folder 9)
  - Catalogs and Mail, 1990-2007
  - Health/nutrition, Undated (Box 550, Folder 3)
    - Health and wellness newsletters and leaflets, 1990-2003 (Box 541, Folder 6)
    - Health catalogs and mail, 1990-2006 (Box 541, Folder 4)
    - Commercial mail, 1995-2005 (Box 541, Folder 1)
    - Media reproduction catalogs and ephemera, 1998 (Box 542, Folder 5)
    - Health and wellness newsletters and pamphlets, 1999 (Box 541, Folder 5)
    - DJ and recording equipment catalogs, 2000 (Box 542, Folder 1)
    - Health/wellness, 2000 (Box 541, Folder 3)
    - Real estate catalogs, 2004 (Box 542, Folder 2)
    - Monolithic domes, 2007 (Box 542, Folder 3)
    - Monolithic domes, 2007 (Box 542, Folder 4)
    - Music and other equipment manuals and catalogs, Undated (Box 541, Folder 2)
- Universal Zulu Nation Documents, 1980-2006
  Arranged alphabetically by title within subject groupings.
  - Infinity Lessons
    - AIDS
      - Africa & AIDS, Undated (Box 506, Folder 20)
      - AIDS, Undated (Box 506, Folder 16)
      - AIDS, Undated (Box 506, Folder 17)
      - AIDS + Saliva, Undated (Box 506, Folder 18)
      - AIDS: Who Invented It and Why, Undated (Box 506, Folder 19)
      - Is AIDS Manmade? The Strecker Memorandum, Undated (Box 506, Folder 21)
      - Puerto Ricans & AIDS, Undated (Box 506, Folder 22)
    - Black Power, Achievement, Thought
      - African Global Unity - Wisdom Divine, 1992 (Box 506, Folder 1)
      - African National Congress, Undated (Box 506, Folder 2)
      - Apartheid Lives in Westchester, Undated (Box 506, Folder 4)
      - The Black family, Undated (Box 506, Folder 5)
      - The Black Oath, Undated (Box 506, Folder 6)
      - Blackout Through Whitewash, 1992 (Box 506, Folder 7)
      - Exposing the Innocent: The U.S. vs. South Africa or the U.S. and South Africa?, Undated (Box 506, Folder 8)
      - The First Americans Were Black, Undated (Box 506, Folder 9)
      - The History of the Zulu Social Aid Club in New Orleans, LA, Undated (Box 506, Folder 10)